Herman Wolf Papers 1985.0008
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series V: Bridgeport: Curran Administration, undated, 1964-1973
  - 1968
    - Speeches (Box 13)
    - State Senatorial campaign (Box 13)
    - University of Bridgeport (Box 13)
    - Urban Coalition (Box 13)
  - 1969
    - Air pollution (Box 13)
    - Annual reports
      - Art work (Box 13)
      - Copy material (Box 13)
      - Final copies (Box 14)
      - Map overlays (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
      - Photographs (Box 14)
      - Sample reports: other towns (Box 14)
    - Attorneys (Box 14)
    - Barnum Festival (Box 14)
    - Bond sale (Box 14)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 14)
    - Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Factories (Box 14)
    - Gimbels (Box 14)
    - Housing (Box 14)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 14)
    - Mayoral campaign
      - Balloons (Box 14)
      - Billboard ads (Box 14)
      - Bottlecaps (Box 14)
      - Bridgeport Citizen (Box 14)
      - Bumper stickers (Box 14)
      - Buttons (Box 14)
      - Campaign dinner programs (Box 14)
      - Election leaflets (Box 14)
      - Emery boards (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
      - Newspaper ads (Box 14)
      - Pocket handkerchiefs (Box 14)
      - Postcards (Box 14)
      - Posters (Box 14)
      - Radio ads (Box 14)
      - Telephone stickers (Box 14)
      - Television (Box 14)
      - Window decals (Box 14)
    - Model cities (Box 14)
    - Musical theatre
      - Bills (Box 15)
      - Musical Events (Box 15)
      - Newspaper Advertisements (Box 15)
      - Promotions (Box 15)
      - Radio Advertisements (Box 15)
      - Releases (Box 15)
    - Narcotics (Box 15)
    - News releases (Box 15)
    - Parks (Box 15)
    - Photographs (Box 15)
    - Redevelopment Agency (Box 15)
    - Showcase Theatre (Box 15)
    - Speeches (Box 15)
  - 1970
    - Biography: Curran (Box 15)
    - Bridgeport Area Foundation (Box 15)
    - Campaign materials (Box 15)
    - Democratic State Platform Booklet (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - Newspclippings (Box 15)
    - Speeches and releases (Box 15)
    - State Senatorial campaign (Box 15)
  - 1971
    - Mayoral campaign
      - Curran biography (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Panuzio, Nicholas (Box 15)
      - Radio spots (Box 15)
  - 1973
    - Mayoral campaign (Box 15)
- Series VI: Connecticut Democratic Party, undated, 1950-1980
  - A History of the Democratic Party, 1967-1968 (Box 16)
  - Attorney General Killian, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Bailey, John: correspondence and notes, 1950-1970 (Box 16)
  - Biography sheets, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Campaign cost notes, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Campaign flyers (Box 16)
  - Campaign handbooks, 1954, 1958, 1960 (Box 16)
  - Campaign observations, 1956 (Box 16)
  - Caucus of Connecticut Democrats Conference, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Caucus of Connecticut Democrats: Founding, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut candidate biographies (Box 16)
  - Connecticu Democratic convention photo, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Democratic News, 1959 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut elections, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut General Assembly, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Connecticut Under Dempsey, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Correspondence: Herman Wolf, 1958-1974 (Box 16)
  - Democratic candidates, 1960-1962 (Box 16)
  - Democratic delegates, 1962 (Box 16)
  - Democratic National Committee
    - "Big Issues" (Box 16)
    - Campaign handbook, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Corrections Please, 1960 (Box 16)
    - Demo Memo, 1968, 1969 (Box 16)
    - Democrat/GOP scorecard (Box 16)
    - Democrat Newsletter, 1961-1962 (Box 16)
    - Democratic Advisory Committee on Nuclear Testing and National Security, 1960 (Box 16)
    - Democratic Advisory Council: policy statement, 1960 (Box 16)
    - Democratic Digest, 1950 (Box 16)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1960
      - Fact Book (Box 16)
      - Rights of Man (Box 16)
      - Fact Sheets (Box 16)
      - Convention Book (Box 16)
      - Official Program (Box 16)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1964
      - Fact Book (Box 16)
      - Official Program (Box 16)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968
      - Fact Book (Box 16)
      - Convention Book (Box 16)
      - Letter (Box 16)
      - Platform (Box 16)
      - Precinct Handbook (Box 16)
      - Press Clippings (Box 16)
      - Temporary Roll of delegates (Box 16)
    - Democratic programs for action, 1960 (Box 16)
    - Democratic state platform, 1960, 1966 (Box 16)
    - National Capitol Democratic Club, 1965-1968 (Box 16)
    - Operation Support, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Summaries of state registration and voting laws, 1960 (Box 16)
    - To Serve the People, 1968 (Box 17)
    - Voter Registration, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Democratic State Central Committee
    - The Democrat, 1950 (Box 17)
    - The Democratic Record, 1961-1963 (Box 17)
    - Officers list, 1966-1968 (Box 17)
    - News releases, 1961-1968 (Box 17)
  - House and Senate candidate list (Box 17)
  - Humphrey, Hubert visit, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Kennedys and Connecticut, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Owens, Howard, 1978
    - Biographical sketch (Box 17)
    - Correspondence and campaign finance (Box 17)
    - Mock-ups and mechanics (Box 17)
    - Pamphlets (Box 17)
    - Photographic file (Box 17)
    - Speeches and releases (Box 17)
  - Party initiatives, 1973-1974 (Box 17)
  - Platform and campaign book, 1954 (Box 17)
  - Platforms, 1960-1974 (Box 17)
  - Presidential visit, 1962 (Box 17)
  - Republican National Committee
    - Chairman Ray C. Bliss, 1965-1968 (Box 17)
    - Chairman's report, 1967 (Box 17)
    - GOP press clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
    - Mobilization of Republican enterprise (Box 17)
    - National Sustaining Program (Box 17)
    - Pamphlets, 1964 (Box 17)
    - Radio-TV campaign manual, 1968 (Box 17)
    - Republican House (Box 17)
    - Coordinating Committee Task Forces
      - Aging, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
      - Cost of living, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
      - Employment opportunities, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Federal, state, local government job opportunities, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
      - Fiscal policy, 1965 (Box 17)
      - Foreign relations, 1965-1968 (Box 17)
      - Gradualism, 1968 (Box 17)
      - Restoration of Federalism, 1967 (Box 17)
      - Revenue sharing, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
      - Water management, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
    - Women's Division, 1960-1968 (Box 17)
  - Republican Party
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Ethnic voter analysis, 1970 (Box 17)
    - Platforms, 1960-1964 (Box 17)
    - Record, 1963-1965 (Box 17)
  - Rules of the party (Box 17)
  - Satellite committees (Box 17)
  - State convention, 1964, 1968, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Statement of vote, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Survey of the political climate in CT, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Vote winners notebook, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Yearbook contract, 1960 (Box 17)
- Series VII: Ways to Win, undated, 1940s-1980
  - Correspondence
    - Book Idea, 1964-1970 (Box 18)
    - Candidate Ad Agencies (Box 18)
    - Candidate Lists, 1960, 1968 (Box 18)
    - Candidate Responses (Box 18)
    - Candidate Survey Letter, 1964-1968 (Box 18)
    - Candidate Survey Summary, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Candidate Thank-You Letters, 1969 (Box 18)
    - Winning Ideas handbook, 1965-1969 (Box 18)
    - Printing costs, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Publishing houses information, 1957-1969 (Box 18)
    - Wolf, David, undated, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Press, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Newspaper Ads, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Newspaper Survey information (Box 18)
  - Outline and Introduction (Box 18)
  - Outline Notes, undated (Box 18)
  - Palm Springs outline, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Working outline, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Chapters 1 - 9 (Box 18)
  - Practical Guide to Politics (chapters 3 & 5) (Box 18)
  - Newspaper Project
    - Outline abstracts
      - Notes from Sullivan (Box 18)
      - Candidate (Box 18)
      - Campaign Organization (Box 18)
      - Nomination (Box 18)
      - Publicity (Box 18)
      - Advertising (Box 18)
      - Gimmicks (Box 18)
      - Election Day (Box 18)
      - Index summary (Box 18)
  - Subjects
    - Absentee ballots (Box 18)
    - Bibliography (Box 18)
    - Billboards (Box 18)
    - Buttons (Box 18)
    - Bumper stickers (Box 18)
    - Campaign costs (Box 18)
    - Campaign planning (Box 18)
    - Clues to support (Box 18)
    - Election day (Box 18)
    - Finance (Box 18)
    - Headquarters (Box 18)
    - Image (Box 18)
    - Introduction (Box 18)
    - Issues (Box 18)
    - Literature distribution campaign (Box 18)
    - Mailing (Box 18)
    - Media contacts (Box 18)
    - Media lists (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 18)
    - News releases (Box 18)
    - Nomination (Box 18)
    - Organization (Box 18)
    - Personal campaigning (Box 18)
    - Picture set-ups (Box 18)
    - Political battle plan (Box 18)
    - Political polls (Box 18)
    - Politics is fun (Box 18)
    - Posters/placards (Box 18)
    - Precinct (Box 18)
    - Press releases (Box 18)
    - Public relations (Box 18)
    - Radio campaigning (Box 18)
    - Special interest groups (Box 18)
    - Strategies (Box 18)
    - Telephone centers (Box 18)
    - Volunteer (Box 18)
  - Candidate Survey
    - Alabama (Box 18)
    - Alaska (Box 18)
    - Arkansas (Box 18)
    - California (Box 18)
    - Colorado (Box 18)
    - Florida (Box 18)
    - Georgia (Box 18)
    - Hawaii (Box 18)
    - Indiana (Box 18)
    - Illinois (Box 18)
    - Kansas (Box 18)
    - Nevada (Box 18)
    - New York (Box 18)
    - Oklahoma (Box 18)
    - Oregon (Box 18)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 18)
    - Utah (Box 18)
    - Washington (Box 18)
    - Wisconsin (Box 18)
  - Congressional candidate file
    - House
      - Bowles, Chester (Box 19)
      - Crellella, Al, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Cotter, William, 1960-1971 (Box 19)
      - Dempsey, John, Jr., 1980 (Box 19)
      - Frasen, Donald (Box 19)
      - Gejdensen, Sam (Box 19)
      - Giaimo, Robert, 1958-1968 (Box 19)
      - Goldblatt, Arthur, 1980 (Box 19)
      - Grabowski, Ben, 1966 (Box 19)
      - Irwin, Don, 1964-1968 (Box 19)
      - LaCroix, Donald B., 1957 (Box 18)
      - Lowenstein, Al, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Lipton, John (Box 19)
      - Lyford, Joe, 1952-1954 (Box 19)
      - May, Ed, 1956 (Box 19)
      - McKinney, Stewart, 1969-1979 (Box 19)
      - Monagan, John, 1964-1970 (Box 19)
      - Morgan, Michael vs. McKinney, J., 1978 (Box 19)
      - Patterson, Jim, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Sadlak, Antoni, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Samuel, Ralph, 1964 (Box 19)
      - Santaguida, Frank (Box 19)
      - Savin, Moe (Box 19)
      - Sibal, Abner, 1960-1964 (Box 19)
      - Steele, Robert, 1972 (Box 19)
      - Tisdale, Charles, 1976 (Box 19)
      - Ward, Pat, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Senate
      - Allen, James, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Anderson, Tom, 1969 (Box 19)
      - Bayh, Birch, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
      - Bennett, William F., 1969 (Box 19)
      - Bible, Allan, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Brown, Horace Seely, 1962 (Box 19)
      - Dirksen, Everett, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Dominick, Peter, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Donahue, Al, 1972 (Box 19)
      - Dodd, Christopher, 1980 (Box 19)
      - Duffey, Joseph, 1967-1970 (Box 19)
      - Inouye, Daniel K., 1968 (Box 19)
      - Kuchel, Thomas, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Lodge, John, 1950 (Box 19)
      - May, Edward, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Miller, Jim, 1976 (Box 19)
      - O'Dwyer, Paul, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Percy, Charles, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Robinson, W. I., 1968 (Box 19)
      - Urbinati, Alfio (Box 19)
      - Weicker, Lowell, 1968-1976 (Box 19)
- Series VIII: Public Relations, undated, 1950-1981
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies, 1964 (Box 20)
  - American Association of Political Consultants, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Advertising Club of Fairfield County, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Baus S. Ross & Company (Box 20)
  - Better Jobs Through Better Understanding (Box 20)
  - Billboard display ratings (Box 20)
  - Bureau of Advertising: 25 Winning Ideas (Box 20)
  - Campaign budget form (Box 20)
  - Campaign button literature, 1960-1978 (Box 20)
  - CCIA, Inc., 1968-1970
    - Campaign catalog, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Congressional Record (Box 20)
    - Computer letter (Box 20)
    - Earphone and attachment monitor (Box 20)
    - Electronic electioneering (Box 20)
    - Election ideas catalog (Box 20)
    - General brochure (Box 20)
    - Political Marketplace (Box 20)
    - Polls and surveys (Box 20)
    - Records (Box 20)
    - Services and materials (Box 20)
    - Telephone and teletalk (Box 20)
    - Videotronic projector (Box 20)
  - Campaign coffee party, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Campaign disclosure, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Campaign novelties (Box 20)
  - Campaign by radio (Box 20)
  - Campaign specialities, 1972-1977 (Box 20)
  - Connecticut voter information: research & statistics, 1954-1980 (Box 20)
  - Do's and don'ts of political endorsement (Box 20)
  - Election timetable (Box 20)
  - Foundation for Public Relations Research (Box 20)
  - Public Relations and the Open Society, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Fund raising fundamentals (Box 20)
  - Galeries Orleanaises, 1953-1964 (Box 20)
  - H & M Association: advertising specialists, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Herman Wolf: public relations, 1950-1974 (Box 20)
  - Independent precinct (Box 20)
  - Workers' handbook (Box 20)
  - Jack Kennedy campaign (Box 20)
  - Millenium Group Inc., 1964 (Box 20)
  - National Imprint Company, 1980-1981 (Box 20)
  - Parthenon Pictures: "Dial V for Votes" (film) (Box 20)
  - Political Science subject file (Box 20)
  - Press
    - Ad rates, 1968 (Box 20)
    - Daily newspapers in U.S. (Box 20)
    - Folio: state of magazine business, 1964-1971 (Box 20)
    - How to Win Votes and Influence People, 1960 (Box 20)
    - National Press Club, 1977 (Box 20)
    - Newspapers in American life, 1971 (Box 20)
    - Type specimen book (Box 20)
  - PRSA
    - Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 20)
    - Publications (Box 20)
  - Pamphlets (Box 20)
  - Report of direct mail advertising, 1964 (Box 20)
  - RNC: Ways to Win, 1967 (Box 20)
  - Source catalog, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Specialty advertising (Box 20)
  - Stationary samples (Box 20)
  - Transportation advertising (Box 20)
  - Television (Box 20)
  - U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Public affairs (Box 20)
  - Women and politics (Box 20)
- Series IX: Political Organizations, undated, 1926-1980
  - Ad Hoc Steering Committee on Human Rights Legislation, 1968 (Box 21)
  - American Association for Social Security, 1940 (Box 21)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1941 (Box 21)
  - American Foundation for Political Freedom, 1955 (Box 21)
  - American Friends of German Freedom, 1950 (Box 21)
  - American Society for the Advancement of the Hebrew Institute of Technology, 1948 (Box 21)
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1949 (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial symposium, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Boy's State, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Caucus of Connecticut Democrats (Box 21)
  - Center for Study of Democratic Institutions (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee for Clean Water (Box 21)
  - Committee of 100 in Support of NAACP Legal, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Common Cause, Inc., 1972 (Box 21)
  - Connecticut for Democratic Action, 1949 (Box 21)
  - Connecticut Citizens for Freedom of Employment (Box 21)
  - Conservative Party (Box 21)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1967 (Box 21)
  - Foreign Policy Association of Greater Hartford, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Forum for Contemporary History (Box 21)
  - Freedom Foundation of Valley Forge, Women's Division, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Hartford Jewish Foundation, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Huntington Civic Improvement (Box 21)
  - Institute for American Democracy, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Institute for Propaganda Analysis, 1940 (Box 21)
  - International Platform Association (Box 21)
  - Laurel Club, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Leadership Foundation, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 21)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1954-1970 (Box 21)
  - League for Mutual Aid, 1940-1964 (Box 21)
  - Mississippi Democratic Freedom Party, 1964 (Box 21)
  - National Committee for Defense Through Education, 1959 (Box 21)
  - National Peace Agency, 1959 (Box 21)
  - National Urban League, 1971 (Box 21)
  - New England Conference of Democratic Electors and Appointed Officials, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Peace and Freedom Party (Box 21)
  - Pilgrim Tract Society, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Rand School of Social Science, 1940 (Box 21)
  - Scholarship, Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality, 1968-1971 (Box 21)
  - Socialist Party, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Taxpayer's Association of Connecticut, Inc., 1971 (Box 21)
  - Union for Democratic Action, 1940 (Box 21)
  - University of Chicago Alumni Association, 1968 (Box 21)
  - University of Pennsylvania Alumni Association, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Urban Coalition, 1968 (Box 21)
  - West Babylon Environmental Communications Institute, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - Westchester Ethical Society, 1954 (Box 21)
  - Woodmere Academy Alumni Association, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Women's Division: Democratic National Committee, 1932 (Box 21)
  - Worker's Defense League, 1964 (Box 21)
  - World Future Society, 1971 (Box 21)
  - World Peace Foundation, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Young Democrats, 1964-1965 (Box 21)
  - Awards, Dinners, Testimonials, Ceremonies
    - American Women in Radio and Television Dinner, 1968-1971 (Box 21)
    - Bailey, John victory dinner, 1954 (Box 21)
    - Bardacke, Gregory testimonial, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Barry, Francis testimonial, 1966 (Box 21)
    - Bridgeport Chamber of Commerce annual meeting, 1955 (Box 21)
    - Bridgeport Wastewater Treatment Facilities ceremony, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Carter-Mondale dinner, 1980 (Box 21)
    - CT State Labor Council convention, 1964 (Box 21)
    - Curran, Hugh charity ball, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Daddario, Francis award dinner, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Debs, Eugene dinner, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Democratic congressional dinner, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Democratic victory dinner, 1962 (Box 21)
    - Dodd, Thomas testimonial dinner, 1965 (Box 21)
    - Donnelly, Joseph (Bishop) consecration, 1965 (Box 21)
    - Fairfield University presidential dinner, 1964 (Box 21)
    - Frassinelli, Attilio testimonial dinner, 1966 (Box 21)
    - Googel, Samuel testimonial, 1961 (Box 21)
    - Governor's inaugural ball, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Grasso, Ella dinner, 1974, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Hartford Democratic Women's Club dinner, 1955 (Box 21)
    - Jepson, Alan inauguration (Box 21)
    - LBJ inaugural ball, 1965 (Box 21)
    - Kennedy, John F. birthday dinner, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Piec, Samuel memorial, 1960 (Box 21)
    - Quinn, Katherine reception, 1961 (Box 21)
    - Reagan, Ronald reception, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1968, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Schaffer, Gloria tribute dinner, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Silver Anvil awards, 1964 (Box 21)
    - South Eastern Massachusetts University reception, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Spear, Eugene tribute, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Women Democratic Leaders tea (Box 21)
    - Women's League of mid-Fairfield open house, 1965 (Box 21)
- Series X: National Politics, undated, 1933-1976
  - 1936
    - American Labor Party (Box 22)
    - Landon, Alfred (Box 22)
    - Communist election platform (Box 22)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
      - Democratic National Committee: The Case Against FDR (Box 22)
      - "They Hate Roosevelt" (Box 22)
      - "He Fights for Labor" (Box 22)
      - "A Rendezvous with Destiny" (Box 22)
      - Roosevelt, F. D. (Box 22)
      - "Spending to Save" (Box 22)
    - The Nation: Party Platforms (Box 22)
    - Republican platform (Box 22)
    - Socialist party platform (Box 22)
  - 1940
    - American Labor Party (Box 22)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (Box 22)
    - New York Committee of Independent Voters for FDR (Box 22)
    - Speakers handbook (Box 22)
  - 1944
    - Picture Digest #2 (FDR) (Box 22)
  - 1952
    - Stevenson, Adlai (Box 22)
  - 1956
    - Americans for Democratic Action: "Nixon: The Second Man" (Box 22)
    - Stevenson, Adlai (Box 22)
    - Democratic National Committee: pamphlets (Box 22)
    - Eisenhower-Nixon inaugural program (Box 22)
  - 1960
    - John Kennedy
      - AFL-CIO voting records: Kennedy-Nixon (Box 22)
      - AFL-CIO COPE: pamphlets (Box 22)
      - Biographical file (Box 23)
      - Citizens for JFK and LBJ: pamphlets, manual (Box 23)
      - Connecticut Kennedy for President Club (Box 23)
      - Eisenhower-Nixon ad casebook (Box 23)
      - JFK cooperation and support (Box 23)
      - JFK pamphlets (Box 23)
      - "New Frontiers" (Box 23)
      - State Central Committee
        - JFK pamphlets (Box 23)
        - Inaugural materials (Box 23)
        - LBJ address: Hartford, CT (Box 23)
        - Newsclippings: JFK (Box 23)
        - Postcards: JFK (Box 23)
      - Social Security during Kennedy Administration (Box 23)
      - U. A. W. pamphlets on Kennedy (Box 23)
      - Visit to Hartford by Kennedy (Box 23)
      - Yale Law Kennedy Club (Box 23)
      - Youth for Kennedy (Box 23)
    - Richard Nixon
      - Biographical information (Box 23)
      - Campaign workers registration cards (Box 23)
      - Campaign pamphlets (Box 23)
      - Convention speech (Box 23)
      - Republican National Committee pamphlets on JFK (Box 23)
    - Stuart Symington Campaign
      - CBS and NBC election handbooks (Box 23)
      - Reader's Digest election handbook (Box 23)
      - Traveler's Insurance Company election handbook (Box 23)
      - UPI election handbook (Box 23)
  - 1964
    - Lyndon B. Johnson
      - AFL-CIO COPE pamphlets on LBJ (Box 23)
      - Biographical file on Johnson (Box 23)
      - Citizens for Johnson Committee (Box 23)
      - Civil rights (Box 23)
      - Democratic National Committee pamphlets on LBJ (Box 23)
      - "Goldwater Made Simple" by Warren Frank (Box 23)
      - Ladybird biographical file (Box 23)
      - LBJ for President newsletter (Box 23)
      - Press clippings on Johnson (Box 23)
      - Summary of Johnson's Senate voting record (Box 23)
      - U. A. W. Citizens Legislative Department (Box 23)
    - Barry Goldwater
      - Republican National Committee: pamphlets (Box 23)
      - "A Choice Not an Echo" by Phyllis Schlafly (Box 23)
      - League of Women Voters (Box 23)
  - 1966
    - AFL-CIO on the right to a Senate Vote re Section 14b of the Taft-Hartley Act, 1966 (Box 23)
  - 1967
    - Democratic Congressional Dinner (Box 23)
    - Legislative (Box 23)
  - 1968
    - Campaigns assessment (Box 23)
    - McCarthy, Eugene
      - Biographical file (Box 23)
      - Connecticut McCarthy For President Steering Committee (Box 23)
      - "First Things First" (Box 23)
      - Letters to voters (Box 23)
      - Pamphlets (Box 23)
      - Press clippings (Box 23)
      - Speeches (Box 23)
      - Voting record (Box 23)
    - McGovern, George
      - Biographical file (Box 23)
      - Campaign workers list (Box 23)
      - Democratic National Committee press releases (Box 23)
      - Editorials (Box 23)
      - Letters to South Dakota voters (Box 23)
    - Kennedy, Robert
      - Assassination clippings (Box 23)
      - Pamphlets (Box 23)
      - Memorial from George McGovern (Box 23)
    - Kennedy, Edward
      - Pamphlet (Box 23)
    - Humphrey, Hubert
      - Visit to Hartford, CT (Box 23)
      - Democratic National Committee support (Box 23)
      - Democratic party kit (Box 23)
      - HHH for President Dinner Committee (Box 23)
      - Endorsements (Box 23)
      - "GOP Platform: Promise and Reality" (Box 23)
      - Herman Wolf correspondence (Box 23)
      - Herman Wolf notes (Box 23)
      - Mayors for Humphrey (Box 23)
      - Humphrey, Muriel (Box 23)
      - New York Citizens for HHH questionnaire (Box 23)
      - Pamphlets (Box 23)
      - Position papers (Box 23)
      - Memorandum (Box 23)
      - Press clippings (Box 24)
      - Speakers kit (Box 24)
      - United Democrats for HHH: "Victory 68" (Box 24)
    - Nixon, Richard
      - Pamphlets (Box 24)